KATE PRASOLEK

kate.prasolek@gmail.com | 07479929600 | London E1 4RS

kateprasolek.github.io/portfolio

linkedin.com/in/kateprasolek

behance.net/kateprasolek

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Reliable graphic designer with a friendly, can-do attitude, experienced in both print and digital design. Self-learner of HTML, CSS and website design with good fundamentals of UI/UX best practices. Creative mind with a natural eye for detail, layout and typography, currently exploring motion design field. Passionate about beautiful designs in any form, e-commerce, good food and cycling.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

| Adobe Photoshop | (4 years) | HTML, CSS | (2 years) | Dotdigital Emails | (2 years) |
|---------------------|-----------|---------------------|-----------|-------------------|-----------|
| Adobe inDesign | (4 years) | Adobe XD | (1 year) | Litmus | (2 years) |
| Adobe Illustrator | (4 years) | Bootstrap | (2 years) | Git / Github | (2 years) |
| Adobe After Effects | (new) | Google Web Designer | (new) | Wordpress CMS | (5 years) |

WORK EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer at Refuse Vehicle Solutions Ltd, Freelance (Mar 2021 - present)

- Website redesign, UI elements and icons creation.
- Create variety of printed and digital assets such as business cards, presentation brochures, website banners, emails and marketing collateral as needed ensuring consistency across all channels.

Graphic Digital Designer at arteKatie Handmade Cards, Self-employed (Jan 2020 - present)

- E-commerce website design and maintenance, update online marketplaces, create social media posts.
- Establish the brand identity, logo design, product photography and photo retouching.
- Produce social media graphics (Instagram, Facebook), banners and promotional marketing collateral.
- Maintain assets libraries and files organised, keep track of sales and expenses.

 I achieved 50% sales and engagement increase by consistent visuals and social media campaigns.

Graphic Designer at Black Women in Leadership Network, Freelance (Nov 2020 - Feb 2021)

- Create digital graphical assets for the website, newsletter and social media channels (Twitter, Linkedin).
- Develop coherent brand guidelines and create easy to use templates.

Graphic Designer at Naturewatch Foundation, Freelance (May 2020 - Oct 2020)

- Communicate with Campaign Coordinator to create engaging website banners and social media assets.
- Design a printed version of the Compassionate Shopping Guide booklet to the brief and budget. I lowered the printing cost by layout changes and offering a different printing company.

Graphic Designer at Wex Photo Video, London, Permanent (Feb 2018 - Jan 2020)

- Create from brief to completion a wide range of marketing communications such as website banners, emails, gifs, brochures, leaflets, magazine's ads, large format prints and more.
- Work collaboratively with other teams and use feedback to produce final marketing creatives.
- Ensure compliance with brand guidelines and design consistency across all formats and channels.
- Manage multiple digital and print projects simultaneously adhering to meet deadlines.
- Supervise magazines' schedules, liaising with publishers and printers.
- Maintain templates and files, where I implemented a system that sped up the team's work-flow.

Freelance Graphic Designer, London (May 2016 - Feb 2018)

Create engaging logos, t-shirts, banners, brochures, leaflets and marketing materials for various clients.

OTHER WORK EXPERIENCE

Receptionist and Research Bank Worker at Poplar Harca, London (May 2015 - Nov 2017)

Reception duties and data administration. I put into practice a structured data entry process, that was easier for volunteers to understand and lower the number of mistakes.

Master Team Member at Paul UK (Jun 2013 - Feb 2015)

Supervising shift, organising displays and stock, handling orders, sales plans distribution, reporting and customer service. I achieved a 5% increase in sales by visually managing displays throughout the day.

Saleswoman at Polkomtel SA (Oct 2010 - Dec 2012)

Phone customer service duties, selling and extending contracts.

Shift Supervisor at Pizzeria laPrimera (May 2009 - Sep 2010)

Organising shifts, stock and deliveries, reporting.

INTERPERSONAL SOFT SKILLS

| Attention to detail | Reliability | Time management | Can-do attitude |
|---------------------|-----------------|---------------------|-----------------------|
| Creativity | Professionalism | Organisation skills | Ability to teamwork |
| Fast-learning | Enthusiasm | Prioritising | Communications skills |

EDUCATION

2016 - 2021 Graphic Design, online learning.

2003 - 2008 Psychology, Silesian University, masters.